{
    "subject": "resource/Atlantic_City_(How_I_Met_Your_Mother)",
    "predicate": "ontology/seasonNumber",
    "object": "2",
    "human_readable": "Atlantic City (How I Met Your Mother) is in its second season.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9098147749900818,
            "question": "In which season does Atlantic City appear in 'How I Met Your Mother'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.77968829870224,
            "question": "What happens during the Atlantic City storyline in 'How I Met Your Mother'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5787144303321838,
            "question": "Why do the characters decide to go to Atlantic City in the second season?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46016666293144226,
            "question": "What is the setting of 'How I Met Your Mother'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3578345477581024,
            "question": "What is the overarching plot of 'How I Met Your Mother'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34882843494415283,
            "question": "Is Atlantic City a significant location throughout the entire series?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33109939098358154,
            "question": "Who are some of the main characters in 'How I Met Your Mother'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2356378436088562,
            "question": "Where do the main characters go on their trip in the second season?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2088777720928192,
            "question": "Does the trip to Atlantic City impact the relationships between the characters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.028808435425162315,
            "question": "What city is famous for its casinos and Boardwalk?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Atlantic City (How I Met Your Mother) is in its second season.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3390_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does the trip to Atlantic City impact the relationships between the characters?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3390_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where do the main characters go on their trip in the second season?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3390_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some of the main characters in 'How I Met Your Mother'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3390_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3390_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3390_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3390_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3390_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3390_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3390_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3390_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3390_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3390_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3390_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided documents mention that the episode \"Atlantic City\" is from the second season of How I Met Your Mother. This information supports the statement that \"Atlantic City (How I Met Your Mother) is in its second season.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}